<archimate:Artifact
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Captive Portal (war)"
    id="id-d2dba3ea13044f5a9d2277a896712259"
    documentation="Default Portal Configuration&#xD;&#xA;The following settings relate to the default type portal configuration:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Network Settings&#xD;&#xA;Use this panel to configure common network web page settings that are shared by both the Assessment / Remediation and the Registration portal web pages.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Administration&#xD;&#xA;Use this panel to configure settings for the Registration Administration web page and grant access to the page for administrators and sponsors.&#xD;&#xA;The Registration Administration web page allows Helpdesk and IT administrators to track the status of registered end-systems, as well as add, modify, and delete registered end-systems on the network.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Website Configuration&#xD;&#xA;Use this tab to configure the common settings used by the different registration web pages, including selecting guest access, authentication settings, and whether assessment and remediation is supported.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Look and Feel&#xD;&#xA;Use the Look and Feel panel to configure common web page settings shared by both the Assessment / Remediation and the Registration portal web pages.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Guest Access and Registration&#xD;&#xA;--- Guest Web Access provides a way for you to inform guests that they are connecting to your network and lets you display an Acceptable Use Policy (AUP).&#xD;&#xA;--- Guest Registration forces any new end-system connecting on the network to provide the user's identity in the registration web page before being allowed access to the network.&#xD;&#xA;Secure Guest Access provides secure network access for wireless guests via 802.1x PEAP by sending a unique username, password, and access instructions for the secure SSID to guests via an email address or mobile phone (via SMS text). Secure Guest Access supports both pre-registered guests and guests self-registering through the captive portal. No agent is required.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Authenticated Web Access&#xD;&#xA;Authenticated Web Access provides a way to inform end users that they are connecting to your network and lets you display an Acceptable Use Policy. End users are required to authenticate to the network using the Authenticated Web Access login page. However, end users are only granted one-time network access for a single session, and no permanent end user registration records are stored. Authentication is required each time a user logs into the network, which can be particularly useful for shared computers located in labs and libraries.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Authenticated Registration&#xD;&#xA;Authenticated Registration provides a way for existing corporate end users to access the network on end-systems that don't run 802.1X (such as Linux systems) by requiring them to authenticate to the network using the registration web page. After successful registration, the end-system is permitted access until the registration expires or is administratively revoked.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;-- Assessment / Remediation&#xD;&#xA;Use this panel to configure settings for the Assessment / Remediation portal web page."/>
